SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS 3
- Responsive frameworks (Bootstrap, Flex, & Tailwind)
- PHP
- SQL / MYSQL / SQLite
- JavaScript
- JSON, & Ajax
- API Integration (with JavaScript Fetch)
- Git / Github / Git Desktop
- E-Commerce Website Configurations (DNS, Nginx, Magento Payment Gateways, Shipping Methods, & more)
- Jira & Confluence
- WordPress
- Adobe Creative Cloud
- Microsoft Office
- Familiarity with Model View Controller app organization
- Local development with MAMP & XAMPP

CONTACT

530.966.6789

Live in Sacramento, CA samvauclain@gmail.com

Portfolio: www.samplacedesigns.com

Sam Place

Web Development & Design

ABOUT ME

I'm an experienced jack of all trades when it comes to the web. I have a solid background in web & graphic design, web development, application support, data troubleshooting, & website configuration.

While I'm grateful to have this diverse work history, I'm working towards specializing more & growing my technical knowledge. Lately I'm gravitating towards web development with PHP, JavaScript, SQL, & APIs. In my off-hours, I've been enjoying learning more about these by building my new portfolio, and am currently enrolled in a web development bootcamp with UC Davis.

RECENT WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Administrator • Jun 2020 - Present

AVB MARKETING

- Configuring websites for 500+ e-commerce clients throughout the US & Canada
- Managing Jira trafficking, administration, & confluence documentation
- Troubleshooting backend & frontend data issues across multiple custom platforms involving several data structures & languages.

Web & Digital Designer • Feb 2017 - Jun 2020

AVB MARKETING

- Building & editing websites using AVB's in-house responsive framework for 500+ e-commerce clients throughout the US & Canada
- Producing promotional graphic design assets
- Trained new designers & wrote process documentation

Contract Web Developer & Designer • Oct 2015 - Dec 2016

ROBERT HALF

- Wrote PHP & JavaScript to fix bugs and improve a WordPress blog for KLOVE
- Video production, web edits, email marketing, analytics, & promotional graphic design for Dignity Health

EDUCATIONAL INFO

Seattle Central Community College, Seattle, WA.

CERTIFICATE IN WEB DEVELOPMENT - 2013

- Dean's List
- President's List

CSU Chico, Chico, CA

BA IN GENERAL MUSIC - 2007

• Dean's List